const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אוֹ',
    answers: ['en'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אוֹת',
    answers: ['teken', 'gedenkteken'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֵל',
    answers: ['God', 'godheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הֵן',
    answers: ['zie', 'kijk'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הִנֵּה',
    answers: ['zie', 'kijk'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'זֶרַע',
    answers: ['zaad', 'nageslacht'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֲצִי',
    answers: ['half', 'helft'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'לָקַח',
    answers: ['hij nam', 'hij haalde', 'hij pakte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מָלַךְ',
    answers: ['hij heersde', 'hij werd koning', 'hij was koning'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מָצָא',
    answers: ['hij vond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נָפַל',
    answers: ['hij viel', 'hij lag'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עָבַד',
    answers: ['hij werkte', 'hij diende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עָלָה',
    answers: ['hij ging op', 'hij reisde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'פָּקַד',
    answers: ['hij bezocht', 'hij zag om naar', 'hij stelde aan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קָרָא',
    answers: ['hij riep', 'hij noemde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁכַב',
    answers: ['hij lag', 'hij ging liggen', 'hij sliep'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁלַח',
    answers: ['hij liet gaan', 'hij zond', 'hij droeg op'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁמַע',
    answers: ['hij hoorde', 'hij gehoorzaamde', 'hij verstond', 'hij luisterde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁמַר',
    answers: ['hij bewaarde', 'hij behield', 'hij bewaakte', 'hij onderhield', 'hij lette op'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson11Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson11-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 11 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson11Vocabulary
